flooranddecor.com 2019-06-08

# Your Privacy Rights | Floor & Decor

Floor & Decor respects the privacy of customers and visitors to our website, which may be accessed at flooranddecor.com or fdcommercial.com and are governed by the [Terms & Conditions.](https://www.flooranddecor.com/policies/terms.html)

This policy governs the collection of information at the websites that link to it, as well as any information we may receive about you. For purposes of this policy, our website includes by definition, any web pages, interactive features, applications, widgets, blogs, social networks, social network “tabs,” or other online or wireless offerings that post a link to this policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology, manner or means.

While offering our website users the advantages and convenience of web-based technologies, we also strive to employ practices that ensure information collected about our customers and visitors is used conscientiously and appropriately.

This policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, other than through our website, such as over the phone, by mail, or in person.

## What information is collected on Floor & Decor’s website?

We collect personal information such as your contact information (e.g., name, e-mail address, mailing address) and billing/shipping information (e.g., payment card number, shipping address). When submitting personal information on an online form, we will identify which fields are required in order to fulfill your request. Additionally, our web server automatically collects click-stream information such as the address (or "URL") of the website that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you have entered on our website.

While shopping or visiting our website, we may ask that you provide certain information. For example, we request personal information when you purchase products or services, sign up for our newsletter, participate in a contest or survey, contact Floor & Decor with a question or concern or apply for employment with Floor & Decor. When you apply for employment, we ask for your job interests, background and resume information, in order to process your application. Floor & Decor may also use third party providers of customer information to improve the accuracy and completeness of our customer database, to increase our understanding of our customers and to identify potential customers.

A "tell-a-friend" tool provided on our website and/or in our e-mails allows you to send information about our products and offerings to another person. You may also be able to ship items to another person. When you use these offerings or when you authorize third party pickup, we may ask you for the name and information of the other person, and that information will be protected pursuant to this privacy policy. You represent that you have the authority to provide us personal information about others.

## How does Floor & Decor use the information collected?

We use the information you provide in order to fulfill requests for products, services or information; personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about the merchandise that might be of interest to you; transmit your data to third party service providers; administer sweepstakes or promotions; tailor advertising efforts; measure and improve the effectiveness of our website, our marketing endeavors or our products or services; tailor our online or in-store offerings to your preferences; administer surveys; and send marketing communications from us or third parties in which we feel you may be interested in or for other business purposes.

## How does Floor & Decor protect customer information?

While we endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive personal information collected on our website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that any information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

## Does Floor & Decor use "cookies" and other tracking tools?

We use technologies on our website to prevent fraud, improve security, assess website performance, deliver content to you that is relevant to what you view on our website and elsewhere on the web, and provide you with enhanced functionality.

A cookie is a small data file that a website may send to your browser and that may then be stored on your device. Our website uses cookies to simulate a continuous connection. Our cookies let us identify you when you use our website and "remember" information about your preferences and past visits, and allow you to move within areas of our website without reintroducing yourself. Most browsers can be set to detect cookies and give you an opportunity to reject them, but refusing cookies may, in some cases, inhibit or preclude your use of our website or its features. To learn more about the use of cookies, including how to manage or delete them, [click here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). HTML (the language some websites are coded in) may be used to store information on your computer or device about your website usage activities. This information can be retrieved by us to determine how our website is being used by our visitors, how it can be improved, and to customize it for our users.

A pixel tag (also known as a "clear GIF" or "web beacon") is a tiny image – typically just one-pixel – that can be placed on a Web page or in our electronic communications to you in order to help us measure the effectiveness of our content by, for example, counting the number of individuals who visit us online or verifying whether you’ve opened one of our emails or seen one of our web pages.

Our website may also use other technologies to track which pages on our website our visitors view. This non-identifiable click-stream data helps us understand how visitors use our website. Our web server automatically collects the address of the website that you came from before visiting our website, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you have entered on our site. Among other things, this information enables Google to generate analytics reports on the usage of our website. To opt-out of your Site usage being included in our Google analytics reports, you may follow [these instructions](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). In addition to Google Analytics, you may have opted into other Google features or applications that interact with our website, such as Google signals, which may associate our or third-party website data with location-based analytics. Subject to your permissions with Google, we may have access to and use such analytics to better serve you marketing information, enhance our website or identify a store location nearest to you. You may access, manage and/or delete this information with Google by visiting <https://myactivity.google.com/myactivity>. Our website (including our mobile site and application) may use location-based services to verify your location, deliver you relevant content and/or advertising based on your location, as well as to share your location with our service providers as part of the location-based services we offer. Further, we or our service providers may use your location information to display our nearest store location to you.

Our “Pro App” may also use location information, including your current location, to allow us to recognize when you have entered one of our stores and to provide certain in-store features or services to you. For example, we may use your location information to recognize that you are in a particular store so that you can notify us that you would like a pickup an order. Before location information can be used for these purposes, you must first opt-in to activate these location-based services within the app. If you enable location-based services in the app, we will automatically collect and may store location information and the MAC address or device ID from your mobile device. We also may aggregate this information, but this information will only be used for our internal purposes and to provide information requested by you. If you do not wish for us to collect and store this information, you may disable location-based services in the app. The use of location based services in the app may also impact the battery life of your phone or device.

The above tracking technologies may be deployed by us and/or by our service providers or partners on our behalf. These technologies enable us to assign a unique number to you, and relate your website usage information to other information about you, including your personal information.

We also contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by participating partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices and Aboutads.info at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our site. Our website does not honor web browser do-not-track settings. Instead, to opt-out of behavioral advertising, follow the instructions above.

## Does Floor & Decor use Third Party Service Providers?

Our website may use third party service providers to serve ads, send e-mails and analyze website traffic on our behalf. These companies may use technologies similar to those outlined above to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites so that we can provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third-party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation and purchases.

## Will Floor & Decor disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

Floor & Decor does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to outside parties. In addition to the kinds of information sharing you might expect, such as displaying what you voluntarily post to public areas on our website, we may share your information:

  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government, judicial or other legal request, or to comply with the law;
  * with credit bureaus, such as late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account; and
  * in connection with a corporate change or dissolution, including for example a merger, acquisition, reorganization, consolidation, bankruptcy, liquidation, sale of assets or wind down of business.

Also, Floor & Decor may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include your name or contact information.

In addition, our website has implemented the Google Invisible reCAPTCHA and the Google Maps API. The use of both are subject to Google's Privacy Policy and Google's Terms of Use. The Google reCAPTCHA collects hardware and software data and sends to Google for analysis to prevent SPAM on contact forms. The Google Maps API is used to provide maps for store locations and to provide autocomplete for inputting street addresses.

## What are the information policies of data collected on social media pages and features?

We maintain presence on several social networking and blogging platforms and we also incorporate some third party social networking features onto our website. Through these platforms and features, we receive some personal information about you and your use of social media. This Privacy Policy applies to that information as well. In addition, third party social networking platforms have their own privacy policies that explain how the third parties that provide them will use and protect your information. In accordance with those policies (and your privacy settings within your social networking accounts) information about your activities on our website (such as "Mary Jane ‘likes’ our tile") may be published to your social network.

## How may customers review their information or request a change of information?

Requests to change or review information may be sent to us using the contact information below.

## How can customers or visitors become informed about changes to the Privacy Policy Statement?

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. In some cases (for example, if we significantly expand our use or sharing of your personal information), we may also tell you about changes by additional means, such as by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address we have on file for you. In some cases, we may request your consent to the changes.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, email and mailing address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (b) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please contact us at legal@flooranddecor.com. We will respond to these requests within thirty (30) days. Requests that come by other means may result in a delayed response.

## How do I contact Floor & Decor?

Please visit our Customer Service Center, <https://www.flooranddecor.com/contact> Effective Date: August 31, 2018
